

Samwel Amwata Software Developer

Contact

Phone:

0725604153

Email:

saseda0@gmail.com

Address

Desai Rd, Ngara, Nairobi.

Website:

https://amwata.github.io/

Languages

English Fluent Kiswahili Fluent Luo Fluent

Skills

Python	85%
Java	80%
Kotlin	75%
JavaScript	90%
MySQL and SQL	85%
PHP	85%
Swift	80%

Profile

I' m a 27 year old male Kenyan citizen with proficiency in IT related fields, including Software Development, Networking, Graphics Design, and Systems Analysis.

Being creative and skillful at problem solving and critical thinking, I'm obsessed with the idea of using software to solve practical problems. I continue to learn new things to stay on edge with ever-changing technology and provide the best.

Experience

Graphics Designer
BlackBerry Enterprise - 2016-2017

Software Developer
Sky Host Company - 2018-2019

Web Designer
Oracom Company - 2019-2020

Education

Diploma in IT Kenyatta University – **2020-2023**

High School
Obera High School - 2012-2015